BRAYAN SANCHEZ

Junior Software Developer

I'm Industrial Technologist with work experience in the administrative area and I'm currently studying Systems engineering. I'm passionate about continuous learning and enjoy the challenges that allow me to develop new skills. I have knowledge in web development, both in the frontend and in the backend, which allows me to address projects in an integral way.

SKILLS

- Intermediate: React.js, JavaScript, Material UI, Jest, Node.js, PostgreSQL, REST, HTML, CSS, Linux, Docker.
- Beginner: Astro, Nginx, GCP.
- English B1.

SOFT SKILLS

Self-taught

• Time management

Communication

Decision-making

Teamwork

EXPERIENCE

For six months, I developed an e-commerce to deepen my knowledge of the PERN stack.

Software developer | Universidad del Valle (Abril 2022 - Enero 2023)

 Made improvements in the design of the university's software that is used by students and professors using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP.

Internship | Abbott - Lafrancol (Junio 2017 - Junio 2018)

Performed administrative tasks as an office assistant.

EDUCATION

Universidad del Valle - Systems engineering (2020 - Actualidad)

Centro Colombiano de Estudios Profesionales CECEP - Industrial Technology (2016-2020)

Learn English - English B1 (2015)